quiz = {
    1 : {
        "question": "question_1",
        "answer": "question_1"
    },
    2 : {
        "question": "question_2",
        "answer": "question_2"
    },
    3 : {
        "question": "question_3",
        "answer": "question_3"
    },
    4 : {
        "question": "question_4",
        "answer": "question_4"
    },
    5 : {
        "question": "question_5",
        "answer": "question_5"
    },
    6 : {
        "question": "question_6",
        "answer": "question_6"
    },
    7 : {
        "question": "question_7",
        "answer": "question_7"
    },
    8 : {
        "question": "question_8",
        "answer": "question_8"
    },
    9 : {
        "question": "question_9",
        "answer": "question_9"
    },
    10 : {
        "question": "question_10",
        "answer": "question_10"
    }
}